[Music]
come on
Jonathan show Mama your
drawing Mama this is you this is me when
I grow up I want to help people just
like
[Music]
you I'm going to work now
but I'm not so sure
anymore why did she become a Financial
Consultant it's not an easy
job sometimes there were
challenges sometimes there were
rejections she worked long
hours in it hasn't been an easy life for
her so why did she become a Financial
Consultant Jonathan an how are you I'm
good heard you have graduated already
and you want to be a Financial
Consultant just like your mother I'm
still thinking about it anyway thanks
for coming to my mother's birthday
party you
know I used to be a very difficult
client
[Music]
M but your
mother is a cal
person who will never give up on her
clients over there thank you
[Music]
Mr Tio don't worry your claims are done
just focus on taking care of your
daughter
[Music]
now I understand what Mama does as a
Financial
[Music]
Consultant she treats her clients like
her own
[Music]
[Applause]
family happy birthday
[Music]
she makes a difference in people's
lives mama I want to be just like you
[Music]